{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830183738","data":{"timestamp":" 947830183738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830261716","data":{"timestamp":" 947830261716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830270950","data":{"timestamp":" 947830270950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830281167","data":{"timestamp":" 947830281167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830294228","data":{"timestamp":" 947830294228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 531e918d-b725-4f7a-9e03-6fb0e45c7d36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830312779","data":{"timestamp":" 947830312779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 531e918d-b725-4f7a-9e03-6fb0e45c7d36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830324149","data":{"timestamp":" 947830324149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 531e918d-b725-4f7a-9e03-6fb0e45c7d36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830350248","data":{"timestamp":" 947830350248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 531e918d-b725-4f7a-9e03-6fb0e45c7d36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830367393","data":{"timestamp":" 947830367393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830381385","data":{"timestamp":" 947830381385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830383457","data":{"timestamp":" 947830383457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830392010","data":{"timestamp":" 947830392010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830394112","data":{"timestamp":" 947830394112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830409004","data":{"timestamp":" 947830409004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830411052","data":{"timestamp":" 947830411052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830418054","data":{"timestamp":" 947830418054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830427512","data":{"timestamp":" 947830427512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830428963","data":{"timestamp":" 947830428963"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830438086","data":{"timestamp":" 947830438086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830439410","data":{"timestamp":" 947830439410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830447326","data":{"timestamp":" 947830447326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830448614","data":{"timestamp":" 947830448614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830460274","data":{"timestamp":" 947830460274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830469247","data":{"timestamp":" 947830469247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830472878","data":{"timestamp":" 947830472878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830484921","data":{"timestamp":" 947830484921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830488175","data":{"timestamp":" 947830488175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830497303","data":{"timestamp":" 947830497303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830500117","data":{"timestamp":" 947830500117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830512031","data":{"timestamp":" 947830512031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830514969","data":{"timestamp":" 947830514968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830523152","data":{"timestamp":" 947830523152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830525105","data":{"timestamp":" 947830525105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830531685","data":{"timestamp":" 947830531685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" b01a4cdd-5752-4f47-ba40-f91528e1cbaa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830541301","data":{"timestamp":" 947830541300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830541534","data":{"timestamp":" 947830541534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830542506","data":{"timestamp":" 947830542505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830543793","data":{"timestamp":" 947830543792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830546756","data":{"timestamp":" 947830546756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830547612","data":{"timestamp":" 947830547611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830547932","data":{"timestamp":" 947830547932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830549178","data":{"timestamp":" 947830549177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830552772","data":{"timestamp":" 947830552771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830553759","data":{"timestamp":" 947830553759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830554024","data":{"timestamp":" 947830554023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830554988","data":{"timestamp":" 947830554987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830557904","data":{"timestamp":" 947830557904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830558946","data":{"timestamp":" 947830558945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830559423","data":{"timestamp":" 947830559422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830564002","data":{"timestamp":" 947830563999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830564103","data":{"timestamp":" 947830564103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" 3b81a763-b019-463a-b756-2cf7ecb8cf56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830687893","data":{"timestamp":" 947830687892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830688412","data":{"timestamp":" 947830688412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830689008","data":{"timestamp":" 947830689007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830689866","data":{"timestamp":" 947830689866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830698082","data":{"timestamp":" 947830698081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830699764","data":{"timestamp":" 947830699764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830700974","data":{"timestamp":" 947830700973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830702750","data":{"timestamp":" 947830702750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830705333","data":{"timestamp":" 947830705332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830707729","data":{"timestamp":" 947830707728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830708220","data":{"timestamp":" 947830708220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830708763","data":{"timestamp":" 947830708762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830709599","data":{"timestamp":" 947830709598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830710166","data":{"timestamp":" 947830710165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830710548","data":{"timestamp":" 947830710548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830713344","data":{"timestamp":" 947830713344"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830714739","data":{"timestamp":" 947830714738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830716478","data":{"timestamp":" 947830716478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830718339","data":{"timestamp":" 947830718339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830719452","data":{"timestamp":" 947830719452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830720478","data":{"timestamp":" 947830720478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830722690","data":{"timestamp":" 947830722689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830723182","data":{"timestamp":" 947830723181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830723669","data":{"timestamp":" 947830723669"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830724330","data":{"timestamp":" 947830724330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830725232","data":{"timestamp":" 947830725231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830728296","data":{"timestamp":" 947830728296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830729721","data":{"timestamp":" 947830729721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830732766","data":{"timestamp":" 947830732766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830739383","data":{"timestamp":" 947830739383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830741082","data":{"timestamp":" 947830741081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830742872","data":{"timestamp":" 947830742872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830743444","data":{"timestamp":" 947830743444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830744137","data":{"timestamp":" 947830744136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830744319","data":{"timestamp":" 947830744318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830745057","data":{"timestamp":" 947830745056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830745474","data":{"timestamp":" 947830745473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830746019","data":{"timestamp":" 947830746019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830747236","data":{"timestamp":" 947830747236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830749419","data":{"timestamp":" 947830749419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830750292","data":{"timestamp":" 947830750292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830751747","data":{"timestamp":" 947830751747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830752826","data":{"timestamp":" 947830752825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830754459","data":{"timestamp":" 947830754459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830755835","data":{"timestamp":" 947830755835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830758850","data":{"timestamp":" 947830758850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830760896","data":{"timestamp":" 947830760896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830762513","data":{"timestamp":" 947830762513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830764725","data":{"timestamp":" 947830764725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830767275","data":{"timestamp":" 947830767274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830769680","data":{"timestamp":" 947830769680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830769746","data":{"timestamp":" 947830769746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830770248","data":{"timestamp":" 947830770248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830770902","data":{"timestamp":" 947830770902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830771185","data":{"timestamp":" 947830771185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830771918","data":{"timestamp":" 947830771918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830772251","data":{"timestamp":" 947830772251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830773065","data":{"timestamp":" 947830773064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830773128","data":{"timestamp":" 947830773128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830773997","data":{"timestamp":" 947830773997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830776484","data":{"timestamp":" 947830776483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830779025","data":{"timestamp":" 947830779025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830780679","data":{"timestamp":" 947830780679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830782874","data":{"timestamp":" 947830782874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830784414","data":{"timestamp":" 947830784414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830789624","data":{"timestamp":" 947830789624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830791253","data":{"timestamp":" 947830791252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830793152","data":{"timestamp":" 947830793152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830794767","data":{"timestamp":" 947830794766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830796913","data":{"timestamp":" 947830796912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830799251","data":{"timestamp":" 947830799250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830799797","data":{"timestamp":" 947830799797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830800500","data":{"timestamp":" 947830800499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830803156","data":{"timestamp":" 947830803156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830804727","data":{"timestamp":" 947830804727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830807174","data":{"timestamp":" 947830807174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830808820","data":{"timestamp":" 947830808819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830809854","data":{"timestamp":" 947830809853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830810361","data":{"timestamp":" 947830810360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830810975","data":{"timestamp":" 947830810975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830811957","data":{"timestamp":" 947830811957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830814737","data":{"timestamp":" 947830814737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830816186","data":{"timestamp":" 947830816186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830817942","data":{"timestamp":" 947830817942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830819991","data":{"timestamp":" 947830819991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830822416","data":{"timestamp":" 947830822416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830824677","data":{"timestamp":" 947830824677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830825171","data":{"timestamp":" 947830825170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830825767","data":{"timestamp":" 947830825767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830826004","data":{"timestamp":" 947830826003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830826642","data":{"timestamp":" 947830826642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830827659","data":{"timestamp":" 947830827658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830830235","data":{"timestamp":" 947830830235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830832781","data":{"timestamp":" 947830832780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830835035","data":{"timestamp":" 947830835035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830837673","data":{"timestamp":" 947830837673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830841039","data":{"timestamp":" 947830841039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830877482","data":{"timestamp":" 947830877481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830879479","data":{"timestamp":" 947830879479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947830879575","data":{"timestamp":" 947830879575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_070508"," gameId":" dc5c243c-81f7-4bcd-9930-9b29e2ed0fae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}